Fernando, what's this
I've found?
-A cellphone.
-No kidding!
I thought it was TV remote.
I know it's a cellphone!
What was it doing
hidden in there?
Is it for talking
to your girlfriends?
-No.
-Are you kidding me?
-No, honey. That's not it.
-It's not?
You probably talk
to your whores on it.
No, I talk to Antonio,
from work, on this phone.
We're on a joint project.
He's on a different provider,
it's cheaper to use this.
I guess Antonio
loves chocolates.
I found the chocolate
next to the phone.
-They were for you!
-You don't say!
And this here?
This, what is it?
I talk to Gustavo on it.
Look... Let me guess.
Surely this
is another provider.
Yes, it's another one.
-I'm calling him.
-No.
We were scheduling a match
on Saturday,
but I got disconnected,
I tried to call, didn't work,
and said: "I'll leave the phone
so you can call me".
You know what? Show me
what's in your pockets.
Get up and take everything
out of your pockets. Go on!
Yes, here it is.
No, there must be more.
These pants have many pockets.
Let's see what you've got.
Look!
Look what I found!
-You organize orgies?
-No.
This is to call my uncle Domingo
in Canada.
It's Canadian. Cheaper.
This is for the dentist,
these are old phones.
-You don't say!
-Yes.
I'll have you know
I found more here.
What is this?
This?
What is it?
On this, you talk
to all your whores, right?
No, these are old phone.
I don't want to dispose of them,
they go into the ocean
and stick into turtles.
I don't want that
on my conscience, Gabriela.
Poor thing!
You have a psychopath, crazy,
insane girlfriend
and you're just trying
to save the turtles.
-I want to save the turtles.
-You're so good!
-Same with batteries.
-Very good.
And this? Why lipstick?
-It's chocolate, honey.
-Chocolate?
You're making a fool
of yourself.
Good afternoon.
Your new phone.
Thank you for bringing me
hemorrhoid medicine!